ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional /4144
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
1941-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Ives, Irving M.
Emerson, Lynn A.
Newfeld, Maurice F.
Shank, Donald J.
Catherwood, M. P. (Martin Paul), 1904-1978
Risley, Robert F.
McConnell, John W.
Moore, David G.
/4144
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8016842
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 06, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8016842
- A-1 Administrative Conferences 1954-'55 through 1956-'57, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A-1 Administrative Conferences 1958-'64, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A-1 Administrative Conferences 1958-'64 continued, 1957-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A-1 Division Directors Meetings 1964-'65, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- A-1 Division Directors Meetings 1965-'66, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A-1 Division Directors Meetings 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- A-3 December 3, 1956 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A-3 May 9-10, 1957 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 8)
- A-3 November 15, 1957 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 9)
- A-3 May 8-9, 1958 Advisory Council, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes news clippings
- A-3 November 14, 1958 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 11)
- A-3 May 21-22, 1959 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 12)
- A-3 Fall 1959 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A-3 April 28-29, 1960 Advisory Council (Box 1, Folder 14)
- A-3 April 28-29, 1960 Advisory Council continued (Box 1, Folder 15)
- A-3 December 1-2, 1960 Advisory Council, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- A-3 May 11-12, 1961 Advisory Council, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- A-3 November 30-December 1, 1961 Advisory Council meeting (New York City) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- A-3 May 10-11, 1962 Advisory Council, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- A-3 November 29-30, 1962 Advisory Council (Box 2, Folder 2)
- A-3 May 9-10, 1963 Advisory Council, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- A-3 November 21-22, 1963 Council Meeting (Box 2, Folder 4)
- A-3 April 23-24, 1964 Council Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- A-3 November 5-6, 1964 Council Meeting (Box 2, Folder 6)
- A-3 April 1-2, 1965 Council Meeting (Box 2, Folder 7)
- A-3 April 1-2 1965 Council Meeting continued, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- A-3 March 10, 1966 Council Meeting (Box 2, Folder 9)
- A-3 March 10, 1966 Council Meeting continued, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- A-4 Correspondence - State University of New York 1956-'62, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- A-4 Correspondence - State University of New York 1956-'62 continued, 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- A-4 State University of New York 1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- A-4 State University of New York 1955 continued, 1953-1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Unsorted Materials I, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Materials for Council Meeting April 27-28, 1967
- Unsorted Materials II, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Materials for Council Meeting April 27-28, 1967 and Discussion Materials ILR Council Meeting December 10, 1968
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1949-'51, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 continued (Box 3, Folder 3)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1952-'53, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- a-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1952-'53 continued, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- A-4 State University of New York 1953 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- A-4 State University of New York - Budget 1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- A-4 State University of New York - Budget 1954 continued, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (I), 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (II), 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (III) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (IV) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (V), 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- A-4 State University of New York - Personnel Policies Committee 1950 (VI) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- A-4a Administration Conference - State University of New York 1957-'63, 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- A-4a Administration Conference - State University of New York 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- A-4b Faculty Senate - State University of New York 1956-'62, 1959-1962 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- A-4b Faculty Senate - State University of New York 1956-'62 continued, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- A-4c Miscellaneous File of State University of New York 1964-'65, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Includes new clippings
- A-4c Miscellaneous File of State University of New York 1948-'64, 1948-1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1961-'62, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1961-'62 continued (Box 4, Folder 2)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1962-'63, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1962-'63 continued, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1963-'64, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1963-'64 continued, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees 1964-'65, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- A-4-4 Material for State University Annual Report - 1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1948, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1949 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1949 continued (Box 4, Folder 11)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1950 continued (Box 4, Folder 13)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1952, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1952-'53, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1953-'54, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1954-'55, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1955-'56, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1955-'56 continued, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1956-'57 [continued], 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1957-'58, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 19557-'58 continued, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1958-'59, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1958-'59 continued, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1959-'60, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1960-'61, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- A-5 Faculty Meetings 1960-'61 continued, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- A-5 1960-'61 ILR Faculty Minutes (extra copies), 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A-5 1961-'62 ILR Faculty Minutes (extra copies), 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- A-5 1962-'63 ILR Faculty Minutes (extra copies), 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- A-5 ILR Faculty Minutes 1962-'63 continued (extra copies) (Box 5, Folder 10)
- A-5 1964-'65 ILR Faculty Minutes (extra copies), 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A-5 1963-'64 ILR Faculty Minutes (extra copies), 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- A-5 1965-'66 Faculty Meetings Minutes (extra copies), 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- A-5 1966-'67 Faculty Meetings Minutes (extra copies), 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- A-5 1967-'68 Faculty Minutes (extra copies), 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- A-5 1968-'69 Faculty Meetings (extra copies), 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1946-'48, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1949 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1950 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1952 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1953 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1953 continued (Box 5, Folder 23)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1954 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1956 continued (Box 6, Folder 3)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1957 continued (Box 6, Folder 5)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting 1958 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting September 1959 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- A-5-1 Annual Faculty Meeting Fall 1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation - Part I and II 1948-'49, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1949 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1951 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1957 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation September 1963 (extra copies) (Box 6, Folder 17)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation September 1965 (extra copies) (Box 6, Folder 18)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1966 (extra copies) (Box 6, Folder 19)
- A-5-2 Faculty Legislation 1967 (extra copies), 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- A-6 ILR Committees (General) 1955-'62, 1955-1962 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- A-6-1 Extension Committee 1960-'63, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- A-6-3 Advisory Committee on Faculty Personnel Policies 1961-'63, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- A-6-3 Advisory Committee on Faculty Personnel Policies 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- A-6-3 Ad Hoc Planning Committee 1959-'61, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- A-6-3a Staff Personnel Policies Committee 1960-'63, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- A-6-4 Building Committee 1953-'61, 1953-1961 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- A-6-4 Dedication (10/2/62) List of Attendees, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- A-6-4 Lists - Dedications and Symposium 1962 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- A-6-4 Lists - Dedications and Symposium 1962 continued, 1946-1962 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- A-6-4 Open House 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- A-6-4 Invitation to Dedication and Symposium Format 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- A-6-4 Symposium and Dedication (10/1-2/62) Attendees, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- A-6-4 Symposium and Dedication - Earlier Correspondence January 1961-June 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- A-6-4 Symposium and Dedication - Earlier Correspondence January 1961-June 1962 continued, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- A-6-4a New Building Naming Committee 1957-'62, 1957-1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- A-6-4a Speicial Events for Labor 1961-'62, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- A-6-4a Open House and Dedication Program 1961-'62, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- A-6-4a Special Events for Management 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- A-6-4a Open House and Dedication Committee 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- A-6-4a Open House and Dedication Committee 1962 continued, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- A-6-4b Dedication Committee 1962, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- A-6-6 Editorial Board ILR Review 1953-'63, 1953-1963 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- A-6-7 Advisory Committee - Labor Management Documentation Center 1952 and 1956-'57, 1952-1960 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- A-6-8 Nominations and Elections Committee 1957-'63, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- A-6-9 Publicans Distribution Committee 1954-'63, 1954-1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- A-6-10 Research and Publications Committee 1954-'63, 1953-1963 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- A-6-12 Social Committee 1958-'62, 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- A-6-13 Undergraduate Program 1959-'63, 1959-1963 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- A-6-14a Visitors, Lectures and Public Events 1961-'63, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- A-6-15 International Activities 1959-'63, 1959-1963 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- A-6-15 Foreign Students Ad Hoc Committee 1960-'63, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- A-6-20 Selection Committee for ILR Dean 1962-'63, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- B-1 Temporary Building 1941-'57, 1941-1957 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Includes several architectural prints and black and white photographs
- B-1 Temporary Building 1941-'57, 1941-1957 (Mapcase folder 15)
- B-1-1 Equipment 1946-'58, 1946-1958 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  Includes architectural prints
- B-3 Building Proposal of ILR 1945 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- B-3-1 Budgets 1946 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1946-'47, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Includes several architectural prints
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1946-'47, 1946-1947 (Mapcase folder 16)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1946-'47 continued, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1948-'53, 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Includes architectural prints; includes news clippings
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1948-'53 continued, 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1948-'53 continued, 1948-1953 (Mapcase folder 17)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1954-'57, 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1958-'61, 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1958-'61, 1958-1961 (Mapcase folder 18)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1958-'61 continued, 1948-1961 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1952-'54, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- B-3-2 Building Plans 1952-'54 continued, 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Cu-1 Cornell Association Council and Corporation Committee 1961-'62, 1949-1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Cu-1 Cornell Association Council and Corporation Committee 1961-'62 continued (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Cu-1 Cornell Association Council, Corporation Committee, and Foundation Gifts 1962-'63, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Cu-1 Cornell University Council 1957-'59, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Cu-1 Cornell University Council Continued 1960-'62, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Cu-1a Cornell University Roster 1955-'56, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Cu-1-2 Cornell Administrative Board 1958-'62, 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cu-1-2 Cornell Administrative Board 1957-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Cu-1-2 Cornell Administrative Board 1962 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Cu-3 Deans Meetings 1960-'63, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Cu-3 Deans Meetings 1953-'59, 1953-1959 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Cu-6 University Committees 1959-'62, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Cu-6 University committees Continued 1951-'61, 1951-1961 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Cu-7 University Development and Relations 1960-'63, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Cu-7-1 University Centennial and Long Range Planning 1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Cu-7-1 University Centennial and Long Range Planning 1961 continued (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Cu-7-1 University Centennial Program 1961-'63, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Cu-7-1 University Centennial Program 1957-'61, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Cu-7-2 Land-Grant Centennial 1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Cu-7-2 Long Range, Centennial, and Accreditation Reports 1960-'61, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Cu-8 University Faculty Meetings 1961-'62, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Cu-8 University Faculty Meetings 1957-'61, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Cu-9-1 Vice President's Office (Zwingle) 1960-'63, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Cu-9-1 Vice President's Office (Zwingle) Continued 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Cu-9-1a Vice President for Academic Affairs (W.R. Keast) 1962-'65, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Cu-9-2 Vice President for Student Affairs (Summerskill) 1958-'63, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Cu-9-2 Vice President for Student Affairs (Summerskill) Continued 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Cu-9-3 Provost's Office 1947-'63, 1947-1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Cu-20 Admissions Office (Secondary School Meetings) 1947-'63, 1947-1963 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Cu-22 Alumni Association 1946-'63, 1946-1963 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Cu-25 Cornell United Religious Work (CURW) 1945-'62, 1945-1962 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Cu-29 Library 1949-'62, 1949-1962 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Includes a newspaper
- Cu-33 Traffic and Parking 1959-'62, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Cu-40 Agriculture 1959-'62, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Cu-40 Agriculture Continued 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Cu-43 business and Public Administration 1956-'63, 1956-1963 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Cu-43a Sloan Institute 1955-'63, 1955-1963 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Cu-44 Education 1954-'62, 1954-1962 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Building and Development Binder, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Cu-46 Graduate School 1957-'63, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Cu-46 Graduate School Continued 1951-'59, 1951-1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- E-1-1 Extension Fiscal 1952-'59, 1952-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- E-1 General 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Includes a memo from December 30, 1952
- E-1-1a Extension Division Programs 1964-'65, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- E-1-2 Extension Courses - Correspondence 1962-'64, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- E-1-2 Miscellaneous Correspondence 1958-'60, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- E-1-2 Miscellaneous Correspondence Continued 1957-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- E-1-2 Courses and Conferences 1957 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- E-1-2 Courses and Correspondence Continued 1952-'57, 1952-1957 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- E-1-2d Extension Courses and Programs 1960, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Includes a pamphlet (probably missorted since its labeled E-1-2a) from 1961
- E-1-3 Extension Staff Meetings 1956-June 1959, 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- E-1-4 Extension Teachers 1950-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- E-1-4 Extension Teachers 1950-'58 continued, 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- E-4 Committee on Labor Education 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- E-4 Committee on Labor Education 1954-'57, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- E-4 Committee on Labor Education 1954-'57 continued, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- E-4 Advisory Committee on Labor Education 1957-'60, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- E-4 Advisory Committee on Labor Education 1957-'60 continued, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- E-5 IULEC (Inter-University Committee on Labor Education) Project 1952-'53, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- G-1-1 All Members of Faculty 1951-'53, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- G-1-1 Adams 1951-'52, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- G-1-1 Adams 1951-'52 continued, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- G-1-1 Adams 1951-'52 continued, 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- G-1-1 A-D 1952-'53, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- G-1-1 E-Z 1952 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- G-1-1 E-Z 1952 continued, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Includes some memos from early 1953
- G-1-1 A-B 1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- G-1-1 A-B 1953 continued, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Includes a few memos from late 1952
- G-1-1 C-K 1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- G-1-1 C-K 1953 continued (Box 11, Folder 11)
- G-1-1 M-Z 1953, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Includes some material from early 1954
- G-11 M-Z 1953 continued, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Includes several memos from late 1952
- G-1-1 Adams, Leonard 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- G-1-1 Alexander. Gabriel 1956 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- G-1-1 Aronson, Robert 1954-'60, 1954-1960 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- G-1-1 Broderick, Walter 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- G-1-1 Brophy, John M. 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- G-1-1 Burling, Temple, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- G-1-1 Campbell, James 1956-'61, 1956-1962 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  Includes several memos from early 1962
- G-1-1 Campbell, Ralph 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- G-1-1 Carpenter, Jesse 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- G-1-1 Catherwood, Martin P. 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- G-1-1 Clark, M. Gardner 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- G-1-1 Collins, Keith 1959 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- G-1-1 Cook, Alice 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- G-1-1 Cullen, Donald 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- G-1-1 Corvini, Rudolph 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- G-1-1 Cutlip, Scott 1956 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- G-1-1 Dietrich, Donald 1959-'60, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- G-1-1 Donovan, Ronald 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- G-1-1 Eckert, Lee 1957-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- G-1-1 Emerson, Eleanor 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- G-1-1 Ferguson, Robert 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- G-1-1 Foltman, Felician 1948-'62, 1948-1962 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- G-1-1 Goodman, Eleanor 1956 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- G-1-1 Frank, Richard 1956 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- G-1-1 Gordon, Richard 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- G-1-1 Gray, Lois 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- G-1-1 Hale, Merle 1956-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- G-1-1 Hanslowe, Kurt L. 1958-'60, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- G-1-1 Hanson, C. Arnold 1956-'61, 1956-1961 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- G-1-1 Hawryluk, Alex 1957-'59, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- G-1-1 Hodges, Wayne L. 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- G-1-1 Jensen, Vernon 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- G-1-1 Konvitz, Milton 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- G-1-1 Landsberger, Henry 1954-'60, 1954-1960 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- G-1-1 MacIntyre, Duncan 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- G-1-1 McCarthy, Philip 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- G-1-1 McConnell, John W. 1957-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- G-1-1 McKelvey, Jean 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- G-1-1 Mesics, Emil 1957-'60, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- G-1-1 Miller, Frank 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- G-1-1 Miller, J. Gormly 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- G-1-1 Morris, James 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- G-1-1 Morrison, Riley 1956 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- G-1-1 Naas, Bernard G. 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- G-1-1 Neufeld, Maurice 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- G-1-1 Ornati, Oscar 1956 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- G-1-1 Patterson, John 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- G-1-1 Perrins, Harlan 1957-'60, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- G-1-1 Radom, Matthew 1956 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- G-1-1 Raimon, Robert 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- G-1-1 Risley, Robert 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- G-1-1 Sayre, Woodrow 1956-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- G-1-1 Slavick, Fred 1954-'59, 1954-1959 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- G-1-1 Smith, Alpheus 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- G-1-1 Tolles, N. Arnold 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- G-1-1 Trice, Harrison 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- G-1-1 Wedlake, Ray 1960-'61, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- G-1-1 Whyte, William F. 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- G-1-1 Windmuller, John 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- G-1-1 Wohlking, Wally 1956-'60, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- G-1-1 Several Members 1958-'60, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- G-1-2 Applicants 1951-'52, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  Includes a black and white photograph; includes news clippings
- G-1-2 Applicants A-B 1958 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- G-1-2 Applicants C-G 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- G-1-2 Applicants H-K 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- G-1-2 Applicants L-N 1958-'59, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 41)